freesamplefinderusa.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy

##   Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**www.FreeSampleFinderUSA.com**

**Policy Last Revised: January 28, 2015**

The following outlines our policy (Policy) for collecting and using information that is personally identifiable to a user (“PII”) and non-PII from our website, www.FreeSampleFinderUSA.com

and the affiliated websites we (Reward Zone USA LLC) operate (collectively, “Websites”).   For purposes of this Policy, PII and non-PII will be referred to as “Information.”  We also describe additional rights that California users have under the California “Shine the Light” law.   

**HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

Here are some of the ways we collect Information from users:

·     Registration forms and surveys;

·     By tracking users’ online behavior on our Websites;

·     Emails, telephone calls, faxes and other contacts with users;

·     Through the use of “cookies” (small text files placed on a user’s computer that enables websites or service providers to recognize a user’s browser and capture and remember certain  information), single-pixel GIF image files (also called “web beacons”) and other technological means; and

·     Information provided to claim a sample using a Free Sample Link.

We place and permit third parties to place advertising and other content, including links to other websites, on our Websites and to promote our Websites.  These third parties, including Google, may collect Information that you provide and may also use cookies, tracking pixels or other technological means to collect Information and to serve ads based on your prior visits to our Website. 

**Cookies.   **We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. You can get more information how opt out of the use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our Websites and/or other sites on the Internet.  You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings or via your browser settings. 

We are not responsible for the Information any of the third parties collect on our Website or for their use of this Information or for the privacy practices of other websites that are linked to our Websites.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Here are some of the types of Information we collect from users:

• Name                                   • Postal address                                 • E-mail address

• Telephone number             • Cell/landline phone number          • Gender and date of birth

• IP Address                            • Survey responses                            • Device ID & location

**Children and Non-Residents** : We don’t knowingly collect or retain information from the Websites from children under the age of 13. The Websites are intended for use by U.S. residents who are not minors. If you are a minor, not a U.S. resident (Canadian residents are not permitted) or don’t agree with this Policy’s terms, please don’t access or use our Websites.

**USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may use Information and share it with third parties in many ways and for many purposes including the following:

•     To maintain suppression or opt-out lists that we may share with third parties so that you are   not contacted when you have asked not to be;

•     For site operation;

•     To provide users with information and/or offers for products or services from us or third parties;     

•     To track online behavior for behavioral advertising and other marketing purposes. Behavioral advertising enables us and our third party marketing partners to deliver to users what is hoped to be more relevant information and/or offers for products or services.  We may share this and other Information we collect with our third party marketing partners who compensate may us.  If you entered your registration information on the www.samplesandsavings.com Website, your email address will only be shared with our mailing partner All Inbox, LLC who may send relevant third party emails on a daily basis;

•      If we are acquired by or merged with another company, we may transfer our users’ information to the acquirer;

•     To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations; and

•     To assist with site operation and other communication services, we may share Information with third parties, including vendors and contractors who provide services to us.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by these third parties as necessary for the purposes set forth above. 

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of your Information. We currently do not encrypt Information that we store.  Given the nature of the Internet, your Information passes through entities that we are unable to control.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee that our security measures or those of third parties who access or transmit your Information will prevent your Information from being illegally accessed, stolen or altered.

**OPTING-OUT**

Users may opt-out from receiving future offers from us by following the Opt-Out instructions contained in the marketing communication or by clicking here.  If you receive offers or other communications from our third party marketing partners and would like to opt-out from future communications from them, you should contact them directly.  A third party’s use of Information is subject to their privacy policy and  we have no control or responsibility over their use.

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

All users who provide their Information to us may modify and correct their Information.  To update or delete your Information, please contact the Privacy Officer by submitting form [here](http://contact.samplesandsavings.com/contact.aspx).

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

The California “Shine the Light” law permits users who are California residents to request information regarding our disclosure of their Information to third parties including the categories of Information shared and a list of the names and addresses of third parties with whom the Information was shared.  If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: www.FreeSampleFinderUSA.com – Privacy Officer, 128 Court Street, 3rd Floor, White Plains, NY  10601.  In your request, please specify that you want "Your www.FreeSampleFinderUSA.com 

 California Privacy Rights Notice."  Please allow 30 days for a response. 

  **Browser “Do Not Track” Signals:   **Most browsers contain a “do-not-track” setting.  In general, when a “do-not-track” setting is active, the user’s browser notifies other websites that the user does not want their personal information and online behavior to be tracked and used, for example, for behavioral advertising.  As required by recent Shine the Light law amendments we are required to inform you that, as is the case with most websites, we do not honor or alter our behavior when a user to our Site has activated the “do-not-track” setting on his/her browser.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may change this Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will post a notice on our Websites and update the revision date which is at the top.  Revisions that expand the types or the scope of our use of the Information we collect will be effective 30 days after posting to a Website and will apply to all Information we collect after the effective date.  Your access and use of a Website following a revision will be deemed your acceptance of such revision. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.

**Questions, Suggestions or to Contact Us:**   If you have any questions, comments, complaints, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or our website, please contact us at Contact US page or www.FreeSampleFinderUSA.com   – Privacy Officer, 128 Court Street, 3rd Floor, White Plains, NY  10601.

Policy Last Revised: January 28, 2015
